{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566037648","data":{"timestamp":" 947566037648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" fdc1094f-b286-4a21-8f96-5e726f546a1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566092720","data":{"timestamp":" 947566092719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" fdc1094f-b286-4a21-8f96-5e726f546a1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566092843","data":{"timestamp":" 947566092842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" fdc1094f-b286-4a21-8f96-5e726f546a1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566102921","data":{"timestamp":" 947566102920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" fdc1094f-b286-4a21-8f96-5e726f546a1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566130293","data":{"timestamp":" 947566130292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" fdc1094f-b286-4a21-8f96-5e726f546a1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566152586","data":{"timestamp":" 947566152586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huyo"," userResponse":" huyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566157248","data":{"timestamp":" 947566157247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fugo"," userResponse":" fugo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566167476","data":{"timestamp":" 947566167476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_pili-lisa-nalo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" pili"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566173757","data":{"timestamp":" 947566173757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_pili-lisa-nalo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566178804","data":{"timestamp":" 947566178804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566207819","data":{"timestamp":" 947566207819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" hili"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566213865","data":{"timestamp":" 947566213865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" naye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566218587","data":{"timestamp":" 947566218587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" saba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566224086","data":{"timestamp":" 947566224085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566229481","data":{"timestamp":" 947566229481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maua_maua-giza-dogo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" maua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566276331","data":{"timestamp":" 947566276331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_vuta-nije-kitu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitu"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566284237","data":{"timestamp":" 947566284237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" kila"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566290032","data":{"timestamp":" 947566290032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" ndio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566296299","data":{"timestamp":" 947566296298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" damu"," userResponse":" siku"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566302344","data":{"timestamp":" 947566302344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" damu"," userResponse":" damu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566308132","data":{"timestamp":" 947566308131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" b419898f-8b1d-4f69-b63c-264a214be8bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566323774","data":{"timestamp":" 947566323774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_damu_tuna-damu-siku"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" damu"," userResponse":" damu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566329587","data":{"timestamp":" 947566329587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" naye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566334121","data":{"timestamp":" 947566334121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huyo"," userResponse":" huyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566351280","data":{"timestamp":" 947566351280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" saba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566357093","data":{"timestamp":" 947566357093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisi_saba-kuyu-sisi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisi"," userResponse":" sisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566363162","data":{"timestamp":" 947566363162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maua_maua-giza-dogo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maua"," userResponse":" maua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566371822","data":{"timestamp":" 947566371822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" ndio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566382179","data":{"timestamp":" 947566382179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_vuta-nije-kitu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitu"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566388155","data":{"timestamp":" 947566388154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_pili-lisa-nalo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566395588","data":{"timestamp":" 947566395588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" mito"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566401792","data":{"timestamp":" 947566401792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566408032","data":{"timestamp":" 947566408032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fugo"," userResponse":" fugo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566413794","data":{"timestamp":" 947566413792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 0ce2abe0-1f38-46c8-8f89-0e49a164460e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566454439","data":{"timestamp":" 947566454439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_haviku__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566478521","data":{"timestamp":" 947566478521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_haviku__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566485263","data":{"timestamp":" 947566485263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_haviku__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566492510","data":{"timestamp":" 947566492510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_haviku__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566494879","data":{"timestamp":" 947566494879"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_haviku__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566507763","data":{"timestamp":" 947566507763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mji__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566509706","data":{"timestamp":" 947566509706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mji__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566520753","data":{"timestamp":" 947566520752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566522923","data":{"timestamp":" 947566522923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nje__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566536063","data":{"timestamp":" 947566536063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_uma___"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566539704","data":{"timestamp":" 947566539703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_uma___"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566542242","data":{"timestamp":" 947566542242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_uma___"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566551263","data":{"timestamp":" 947566551263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ko__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566553356","data":{"timestamp":" 947566553356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ko__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566566726","data":{"timestamp":" 947566566725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kukusanyi__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566568988","data":{"timestamp":" 947566568988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kukusanyi__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566597608","data":{"timestamp":" 947566597608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mza__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566599499","data":{"timestamp":" 947566599499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mza__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566606322","data":{"timestamp":" 947566606322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_mza__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566616514","data":{"timestamp":" 947566616514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566623195","data":{"timestamp":" 947566623195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566625532","data":{"timestamp":" 947566625532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566627372","data":{"timestamp":" 947566627372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ikavu___"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566641386","data":{"timestamp":" 947566641386"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dema__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566643452","data":{"timestamp":" 947566643452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_dema__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566655679","data":{"timestamp":" 947566655679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566658719","data":{"timestamp":" 947566658719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566673585","data":{"timestamp":" 947566673585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566677524","data":{"timestamp":" 947566677523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:1.0.1.fin.v","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566694576","data":{"timestamp":" 947566694573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" f14d5998-58b3-4b91-b13d-93b107f05bbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_1.0.1.fin.v"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write____"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566712242","data":{"timestamp":" 947566712241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 6ec6a6d4-3fd1-46b5-b298-c6d49747b6c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_chao-haha-mito"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566716688","data":{"timestamp":" 947566716688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 6ec6a6d4-3fd1-46b5-b298-c6d49747b6c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huyo_huyo-kufa-nini"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huyo"," userResponse":" huyo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566724308","data":{"timestamp":" 947566724308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 6ec6a6d4-3fd1-46b5-b298-c6d49747b6c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naye_wana-naye-hili"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naye"," userResponse":" naye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566729664","data":{"timestamp":" 947566729664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 6ec6a6d4-3fd1-46b5-b298-c6d49747b6c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndio_nane-ndio-kila"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndio"," userResponse":" ndio"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566735254","data":{"timestamp":" 947566735253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 6ec6a6d4-3fd1-46b5-b298-c6d49747b6c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kitu_vuta-nije-kitu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitu"," userResponse":" kitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566746452","data":{"timestamp":" 947566746452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 6ec6a6d4-3fd1-46b5-b298-c6d49747b6c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fugo"," userResponse":" lake"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566765262","data":{"timestamp":" 947566765261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 6ec6a6d4-3fd1-46b5-b298-c6d49747b6c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.4.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_fugo_lake-dogo-fugo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566782135","data":{"timestamp":" 947566782134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566782733","data":{"timestamp":" 947566782732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566783398","data":{"timestamp":" 947566783397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566783547","data":{"timestamp":" 947566783546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566783932","data":{"timestamp":" 947566783932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566784349","data":{"timestamp":" 947566784348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566785469","data":{"timestamp":" 947566785468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566786483","data":{"timestamp":" 947566786482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TUKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566787068","data":{"timestamp":" 947566787067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566787238","data":{"timestamp":" 947566787238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566788072","data":{"timestamp":" 947566788072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566795976","data":{"timestamp":" 947566795975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566799251","data":{"timestamp":" 947566799250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566800203","data":{"timestamp":" 947566800202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566801051","data":{"timestamp":" 947566801051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566801857","data":{"timestamp":" 947566801857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566803186","data":{"timestamp":" 947566803186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566804790","data":{"timestamp":" 947566804790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566806478","data":{"timestamp":" 947566806478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566808082","data":{"timestamp":" 947566808081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" TUKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566809448","data":{"timestamp":" 947566809448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566810505","data":{"timestamp":" 947566810504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566811107","data":{"timestamp":" 947566811107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mimi na dada yangu tulikuwa tukitembea karibu na barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566813386","data":{"timestamp":" 947566813385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566814409","data":{"timestamp":" 947566814408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566815440","data":{"timestamp":" 947566815437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566816510","data":{"timestamp":" 947566816510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIENDESHWA"," userResponse":" IKIENDESHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566817749","data":{"timestamp":" 947566817748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEREMKA"," userResponse":" KUTEREMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566818339","data":{"timestamp":" 947566818339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566820286","data":{"timestamp":" 947566820286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566821029","data":{"timestamp":" 947566821028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566829825","data":{"timestamp":" 947566829824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566834698","data":{"timestamp":" 947566834697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566836330","data":{"timestamp":" 947566836329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" IKIENDESHWA"," userResponse":" START_IKIENDESHWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566838790","data":{"timestamp":" 947566838790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" IKIENDESHWA"," userResponse":" START_IKIENDESHWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566840664","data":{"timestamp":" 947566840663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIENDESHWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566842338","data":{"timestamp":" 947566842337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEREMKA"," userResponse":" KUTEREMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566843842","data":{"timestamp":" 947566843842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori kubwa ilikuwa ikiendeshwa kuteremka mlima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566846023","data":{"timestamp":" 947566846022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566846518","data":{"timestamp":" 947566846517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566847327","data":{"timestamp":" 947566847327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566848598","data":{"timestamp":" 947566848597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" LIKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566849456","data":{"timestamp":" 947566849455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566849671","data":{"timestamp":" 947566849671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566850331","data":{"timestamp":" 947566850330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566850750","data":{"timestamp":" 947566850750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566851492","data":{"timestamp":" 947566851492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566851801","data":{"timestamp":" 947566851800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566852613","data":{"timestamp":" 947566852612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566854613","data":{"timestamp":" 947566854613"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566854943","data":{"timestamp":" 947566854943"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566856617","data":{"timestamp":" 947566856617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566858642","data":{"timestamp":" 947566858642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" LIKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566859416","data":{"timestamp":" 947566859415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566861242","data":{"timestamp":" 947566861242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566862420","data":{"timestamp":" 947566862420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566863527","data":{"timestamp":" 947566863527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566864146","data":{"timestamp":" 947566864146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566865271","data":{"timestamp":" 947566865271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566867131","data":{"timestamp":" 947566867131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566867549","data":{"timestamp":" 947566867549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari ndogo lilikuwa likielekea upande wa juu wa barabara kwa kasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566869971","data":{"timestamp":" 947566869970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566870151","data":{"timestamp":" 947566870151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566870682","data":{"timestamp":" 947566870682"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566871377","data":{"timestamp":" 947566871376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566872766","data":{"timestamp":" 947566872766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566873367","data":{"timestamp":" 947566873366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566873866","data":{"timestamp":" 947566873866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566874105","data":{"timestamp":" 947566874105"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566874874","data":{"timestamp":" 947566874873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNUNU"," userResponse":" RUNUNU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566877112","data":{"timestamp":" 947566877111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566877443","data":{"timestamp":" 947566877443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566877831","data":{"timestamp":" 947566877831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566879239","data":{"timestamp":" 947566879239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566880567","data":{"timestamp":" 947566880567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" START_AKIZUNGUMZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566881704","data":{"timestamp":" 947566881704"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," userResponse":" AKIZUNGUMZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566883728","data":{"timestamp":" 947566883728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566883757","data":{"timestamp":" 947566883756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566884127","data":{"timestamp":" 947566884127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566885970","data":{"timestamp":" 947566885970"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566888002","data":{"timestamp":" 947566888002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dereva wa lori alikuwa akizungumza kwa simu ya rununu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNUNU"," userResponse":" RUNUNU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566890013","data":{"timestamp":" 947566890012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566891206","data":{"timestamp":" 947566891206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZINGATIA"," userResponse":" AKIZINGATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566892023","data":{"timestamp":" 947566892022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566894185","data":{"timestamp":" 947566894184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566894777","data":{"timestamp":" 947566894776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZINGATIA"," userResponse":" START_AKIZINGATIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566895991","data":{"timestamp":" 947566895990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZINGATIA"," userResponse":" START_AKIZINGATIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566897958","data":{"timestamp":" 947566897957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIZINGATIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566900537","data":{"timestamp":" 947566900537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuwa akizingatia barabara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARABARA"," userResponse":" BARABARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566903370","data":{"timestamp":" 947566903369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566904577","data":{"timestamp":" 947566904576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIGONGA"," userResponse":" LILIGONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566904922","data":{"timestamp":" 947566904921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566908137","data":{"timestamp":" 947566908137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566909543","data":{"timestamp":" 947566909543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIGONGA"," userResponse":" LILIGONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566910167","data":{"timestamp":" 947566910166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori liligonga gari!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566912473","data":{"timestamp":" 947566912472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566912561","data":{"timestamp":" 947566912561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566913702","data":{"timestamp":" 947566913701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566914581","data":{"timestamp":" 947566914580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566914798","data":{"timestamp":" 947566914798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566915748","data":{"timestamp":" 947566915747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566917210","data":{"timestamp":" 947566917209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566918215","data":{"timestamp":" 947566918214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" KUTOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566919644","data":{"timestamp":" 947566919643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566921758","data":{"timestamp":" 947566921757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566923050","data":{"timestamp":" 947566923049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566924652","data":{"timestamp":" 947566924651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566926891","data":{"timestamp":" 947566926890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566927255","data":{"timestamp":" 947566927255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566929784","data":{"timestamp":" 947566929783"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566930922","data":{"timestamp":" 947566930922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566933440","data":{"timestamp":" 947566933440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566938528","data":{"timestamp":" 947566938528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566940260","data":{"timestamp":" 947566940260"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566940556","data":{"timestamp":" 947566940556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566941732","data":{"timestamp":" 947566941732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" START_WALIFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566943403","data":{"timestamp":" 947566943402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566944089","data":{"timestamp":" 947566944089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" WALIFIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566945964","data":{"timestamp":" 947566945964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566947400","data":{"timestamp":" 947566947398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566948392","data":{"timestamp":" 947566948392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la hospitali pamoja na polisi walifika kutoa usaidizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAIDIZI"," userResponse":" USAIDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566951364","data":{"timestamp":" 947566951363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566952229","data":{"timestamp":" 947566952228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWILI"," userResponse":" MAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566952333","data":{"timestamp":" 947566952332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566952989","data":{"timestamp":" 947566952989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTA"," userResponse":" KUVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566953849","data":{"timestamp":" 947566953848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566954908","data":{"timestamp":" 947566954907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIFIKA"," userResponse":" YALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566957087","data":{"timestamp":" 947566957087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" START_MAGARI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566958250","data":{"timestamp":" 947566958250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAWILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566959830","data":{"timestamp":" 947566959830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566962572","data":{"timestamp":" 947566962572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAWILI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566964558","data":{"timestamp":" 947566964558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWILI"," userResponse":" MAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566965920","data":{"timestamp":" 947566965920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566966644","data":{"timestamp":" 947566966644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTA"," userResponse":" KUVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566968050","data":{"timestamp":" 947566968049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGARI"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566969963","data":{"timestamp":" 947566969963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Magari mawili ya kuvuta magari yalifika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIFIKA"," userResponse":" YALIFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566971676","data":{"timestamp":" 947566971676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566972587","data":{"timestamp":" 947566972586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIVUTA"," userResponse":" LILIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566973104","data":{"timestamp":" 947566973103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566975435","data":{"timestamp":" 947566975435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MAGARI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566977409","data":{"timestamp":" 947566977408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566983106","data":{"timestamp":" 947566983106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIVUTA"," userResponse":" LILIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566983746","data":{"timestamp":" 947566983746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Moja lilivuta lori."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566985754","data":{"timestamp":" 947566985753"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566986718","data":{"timestamp":" 947566986718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAVUTA"," userResponse":" LIKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566987134","data":{"timestamp":" 947566987134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566988989","data":{"timestamp":" 947566988988"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGINE"," userResponse":" LINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566990252","data":{"timestamp":" 947566990252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKAVUTA"," userResponse":" LIKAVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566990666","data":{"timestamp":" 947566990666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lingine likavuta gari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566993291","data":{"timestamp":" 947566993290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566993736","data":{"timestamp":" 947566993735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566994303","data":{"timestamp":" 947566994303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566998284","data":{"timestamp":" 947566998284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566999385","data":{"timestamp":" 947566999385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947566999692","data":{"timestamp":" 947566999692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tuliona kila kitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567002144","data":{"timestamp":" 947567002143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULITISHIKA"," userResponse":" TULITISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567002669","data":{"timestamp":" 947567002668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567010910","data":{"timestamp":" 947567010910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULITISHIKA"," userResponse":" TULITISHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567011611","data":{"timestamp":" 947567011611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567013623","data":{"timestamp":" 947567013622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567013756","data":{"timestamp":" 947567013755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567029939","data":{"timestamp":" 947567029938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8dc41573-fac7-42a1-bdf9-7128d66823fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567045052","data":{"timestamp":" 947567045052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567054533","data":{"timestamp":" 947567054533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567056143","data":{"timestamp":" 947567056143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwito"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITO"," userResponse":" MWITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567059949","data":{"timestamp":" 947567059949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwito"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITO"," userResponse":" MWITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567061526","data":{"timestamp":" 947567061526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sketi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SKETI"," userResponse":" SKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567064791","data":{"timestamp":" 947567064790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sketi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SKETI"," userResponse":" SKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567066412","data":{"timestamp":" 947567066411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chuma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567069692","data":{"timestamp":" 947567069692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chuma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567071296","data":{"timestamp":" 947567071295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567075884","data":{"timestamp":" 947567075883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wenye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567077488","data":{"timestamp":" 947567077487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567082912","data":{"timestamp":" 947567082912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" START_IKIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567085448","data":{"timestamp":" 947567085448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ikiwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567087066","data":{"timestamp":" 947567087066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567090678","data":{"timestamp":" 947567090677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567092282","data":{"timestamp":" 947567092281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567094714","data":{"timestamp":" 947567094713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567096315","data":{"timestamp":" 947567096314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567098896","data":{"timestamp":" 947567098896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567100488","data":{"timestamp":" 947567100487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567103527","data":{"timestamp":" 947567103526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567105553","data":{"timestamp":" 947567105552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567105660","data":{"timestamp":" 947567105660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 5927c0d4-f87f-44de-b483-858f9a72d916"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__HF.wrd.len-5.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567122862","data":{"timestamp":" 947567122861"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567123118","data":{"timestamp":" 947567123117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567124137","data":{"timestamp":" 947567124136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DINASOU"," userResponse":" DINASOU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567124713","data":{"timestamp":" 947567124712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567126884","data":{"timestamp":" 947567126883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567127524","data":{"timestamp":" 947567127524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567128304","data":{"timestamp":" 947567128303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567134202","data":{"timestamp":" 947567134202"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567141306","data":{"timestamp":" 947567141305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567142126","data":{"timestamp":" 947567142126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" DINASOU"," userResponse":" START_DINASOU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567144371","data":{"timestamp":" 947567144371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DINASOU"," userResponse":" DINASOU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567145289","data":{"timestamp":" 947567145288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567147168","data":{"timestamp":" 947567147167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567150910","data":{"timestamp":" 947567150910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," userResponse":" TUNAWAANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567152328","data":{"timestamp":" 947567152327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567152428","data":{"timestamp":" 947567152427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567153895","data":{"timestamp":" 947567153895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Dinasou wangu tunawaangalia ndege angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567156299","data":{"timestamp":" 947567156298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567156544","data":{"timestamp":" 947567156543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567157172","data":{"timestamp":" 947567157171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567157758","data":{"timestamp":" 947567157757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567159223","data":{"timestamp":" 947567159222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMKUTA"," userResponse":" TUNAMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567159800","data":{"timestamp":" 947567159798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" SOKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567160616","data":{"timestamp":" 947567160616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567162657","data":{"timestamp":" 947567162657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567163156","data":{"timestamp":" 947567163155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567163417","data":{"timestamp":" 947567163416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567163747","data":{"timestamp":" 947567163747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567165638","data":{"timestamp":" 947567165638"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567167133","data":{"timestamp":" 947567167133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567168215","data":{"timestamp":" 947567168215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAMKUTA"," userResponse":" TUNAMKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567169799","data":{"timestamp":" 947567169799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" SOKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567170308","data":{"timestamp":" 947567170307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Ndege wangu tunamkuta Sokwe mtini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTINI"," userResponse":" MTINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567172620","data":{"timestamp":" 947567172620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567173639","data":{"timestamp":" 947567173637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINACHEZA"," userResponse":" NINACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567173836","data":{"timestamp":" 947567173835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567174494","data":{"timestamp":" 947567174494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" SOKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567174992","data":{"timestamp":" 947567174991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567175538","data":{"timestamp":" 947567175536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567176218","data":{"timestamp":" 947567176218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567177026","data":{"timestamp":" 947567177025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567178918","data":{"timestamp":" 947567178918"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567179622","data":{"timestamp":" 947567179622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINACHEZA"," userResponse":" NINACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567180018","data":{"timestamp":" 947567180017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567181521","data":{"timestamp":" 947567181521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOKWE"," userResponse":" SOKWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567182426","data":{"timestamp":" 947567182426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567182930","data":{"timestamp":" 947567182929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567184439","data":{"timestamp":" 947567184438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567186532","data":{"timestamp":" 947567186531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninacheza na Sokwe na twiga wangu milimani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567188909","data":{"timestamp":" 947567188909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567189453","data":{"timestamp":" 947567189452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567190155","data":{"timestamp":" 947567190154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567190783","data":{"timestamp":" 947567190782"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567191981","data":{"timestamp":" 947567191980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" WANAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567192526","data":{"timestamp":" 947567192525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567193186","data":{"timestamp":" 947567193185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567193536","data":{"timestamp":" 947567193535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567194064","data":{"timestamp":" 947567194064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567194615","data":{"timestamp":" 947567194614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567197729","data":{"timestamp":" 947567197728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567199398","data":{"timestamp":" 947567199398"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567200735","data":{"timestamp":" 947567200735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567201987","data":{"timestamp":" 947567201987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567203426","data":{"timestamp":" 947567203426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567204394","data":{"timestamp":" 947567204393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567205110","data":{"timestamp":" 947567205109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567206407","data":{"timestamp":" 947567206407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" WANAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567207121","data":{"timestamp":" 947567207121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567208028","data":{"timestamp":" 947567208028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567209000","data":{"timestamp":" 947567208999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567210585","data":{"timestamp":" 947567210584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567211517","data":{"timestamp":" 947567211516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567212910","data":{"timestamp":" 947567212910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567214543","data":{"timestamp":" 947567214543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567216654","data":{"timestamp":" 947567216654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567219032","data":{"timestamp":" 947567219032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567219269","data":{"timestamp":" 947567219268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567219864","data":{"timestamp":" 947567219863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567220390","data":{"timestamp":" 947567220389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567221827","data":{"timestamp":" 947567221826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567222602","data":{"timestamp":" 947567222601"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567223003","data":{"timestamp":" 947567223002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567223610","data":{"timestamp":" 947567223610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567224078","data":{"timestamp":" 947567224078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567224742","data":{"timestamp":" 947567224742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567227426","data":{"timestamp":" 947567227426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567227827","data":{"timestamp":" 947567227827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567228322","data":{"timestamp":" 947567228322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567231027","data":{"timestamp":" 947567231026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" START_WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567233475","data":{"timestamp":" 947567233475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567235362","data":{"timestamp":" 947567235361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567236702","data":{"timestamp":" 947567236701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567240583","data":{"timestamp":" 947567240583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567240880","data":{"timestamp":" 947567240880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567242385","data":{"timestamp":" 947567242385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567243359","data":{"timestamp":" 947567243358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567243830","data":{"timestamp":" 947567243830"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567245476","data":{"timestamp":" 947567245476"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Kima wangu tunakula ndizi na Nyani kila siku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567247869","data":{"timestamp":" 947567247868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567248415","data":{"timestamp":" 947567248415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567249113","data":{"timestamp":" 947567249112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567249743","data":{"timestamp":" 947567249740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567250945","data":{"timestamp":" 947567250944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" WANAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567251492","data":{"timestamp":" 947567251491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567252155","data":{"timestamp":" 947567252154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567252503","data":{"timestamp":" 947567252503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567253030","data":{"timestamp":" 947567253030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567253576","data":{"timestamp":" 947567253576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567257037","data":{"timestamp":" 947567257036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567259431","data":{"timestamp":" 947567259431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567261693","data":{"timestamp":" 947567261692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567264066","data":{"timestamp":" 947567264066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567266632","data":{"timestamp":" 947567266631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOGOPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567269945","data":{"timestamp":" 947567269944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567272238","data":{"timestamp":" 947567272238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567277758","data":{"timestamp":" 947567277757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567278520","data":{"timestamp":" 947567278519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567279277","data":{"timestamp":" 947567279277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567281808","data":{"timestamp":" 947567281808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyani wangu na Kima wanaogopa Bwana Kobe kwa kila njia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567282952","data":{"timestamp":" 947567282952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" NYANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567283775","data":{"timestamp":" 947567283775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567283930","data":{"timestamp":" 947567283930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567284289","data":{"timestamp":" 947567284288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567284390","data":{"timestamp":" 947567284390"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWAPENDA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567284573","data":{"timestamp":" 947567284573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSONYA"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567284792","data":{"timestamp":" 947567284792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TWAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567285033","data":{"timestamp":" 947567285033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIMBA"," userResponse":" KUSONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567285438","data":{"timestamp":" 947567285438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIMBO"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567285589","data":{"timestamp":" 947567285589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANDO"," userResponse":" KUIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567285715","data":{"timestamp":" 947567285715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NYIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567286198","data":{"timestamp":" 947567286198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567381393","data":{"timestamp":" 947567381393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947567381501","data":{"timestamp":" 947567381501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000111_074706"," gameId":" 8ca972bd-2ebc-47e5-a34b-d9da702816fe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Nyoka nami twapenda kusonya na kuimba nyimbo kando ya ziwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" KANDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}